## Aigboje Ohiorenua

Full Stack Developer

## CONTACT

**Address** 

Edo State, Nigeria

**Postal Code** 

Benin City: 300251

E-mail

aigbojeohiorenua@gmail.co

<u>m</u>

Git Repo

https://github.com/Ohior

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ohiorenua-aigboje-a79b6a2

Blog

https://ohiscode.hashnode.dev/

**SKILLS** 

Python 98%

**Java 92%** 

Kotlin 95%

SQL/MySQL 95%

Postgres 80%

**Javascript 60%** 

Unity 70%

Flutter 70%

Csharp 85%

**Cpp 60%** 

**Cloud Storage 90%** 

**Local Storage 95%** 

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an experienced Self taught Developer with an extended knowledge of programming, desktop application, web applications, and mobile application. With a diverse and promising set of skills. Competent in a variety of platforms, programming languages, and embedded systems.

Capable of managing myself effectively during independent projects as well as collaborating with a team.

I also have over 6 years of experience in programming and design. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

## **WORK HISTORY**

01-2018 -05-2022 Web Developer

Full stack, Benin City

- I contributed to the python Flask framework. This you can find in my repository
- Removing and fixing bugs from a collaborated Django project.
- I am able to work with a team and also work as a lone wolf, being a full stack developer.
- My strength lies on the backend of development. This makes My code very readable and well documented.
- I found and contributed to the fixing of a css bug in my hackathon challenge. This proves my ability to work on the front end.
- Development and adding a chatting functionality to the mobile application
- Contributed to the splinter python framework which is use for web scraping

02-2015 -11-2020 Software Developer Benin City

- Contributed to the design and development of desktop messenger application.
- With the use of Kotlin, I developed a marketplace mobile application, where sellers and buyers can meet
- With the use of Flutter I developed a facebook clone to show how skillful I am with flutter
- With the use of flutter I have developed a cross platform application, which is very responsive.
- By attempting to try a new skill I developed a mobile game with unity engine, using C#.
- Created a module that fixed the issue of the tkinter menu not being able to display color in Windows. <a href="link">link</a>

## **EDUCATION**

2012 -2015 Senior School Certificate, Edo State, Nigeria

OTHER SKILLS

Django, Flask, Gimp, Blender, Microsoft-word, HTML, CSS, ElectronJS, Swing, JavaFX, Pygame, Kivy, SQLite, JSON, Android Development, iOS Development, Web APIs, Mobile APIs, GUI, UI & UX Design, Firebase, Database, Document Design, SQL